HERES
THE
BRAINROT
STYLE
MONOLOGUE
YOOO
WHATS
GOOD
FAM
ITS
YOUR
BOY
BACK
WITH
THE
DAILY
BRAINROT
FOR
FEB
TWENTY
SIXTH
TWO
THOUSAND
AND
TWENTY
FIFTH
COVER
IN
AI
CRYPTO
AND
TECH
NEWS
FIRST
OFF
TRUMP
JUST
ANNOUNCED
THE
GOLD
CARD
PROGRAM
WHERE
FOREIGNERS
CAN
PAY
FIFTH
MILLION
TO
ENTER
THE
US
AND
CREATE
JOBS
LIKE
IS
THIS
A
NEW
FORM
OF
IMMIGRATION
OR
JUST
A
WAY
TO
MAKE
SOME
EXTRA
CASH
MEANWHILE
ISRAEL
AND
HAMAS
AGREED
ON
A
PRISONER
EXCHANGE
MAINTAINING
THAT
FRAGILE
CEASEFIRE
THAT
ENDED
FIFTEENTH
MONTHS
OF
CONFLICT
AND
TAIWAN
DETAINED
EIGHT
CHINESE
NATIONALS
AFTER
AN
UNDERSEA
COMMUNICATIONS
CABLE
WAS
CUT
WHATS
GOING
ON
IN
THE
WORLD
MAN
NOW
LETS
TALK
TECH
MERCEDESBENZ
IS
TESTING
SOLIDSTATE
BATTERIES
EXTENDING
EV
RANGE
BY
TWENTY
FIFTH
TO
ONE
THOUSANDTH
KILOMETERS
THATS
LIKE
A
WHOLE
NEW
LEVEL
OF
ELECTRIC
VEHICLES
BRO
GOOGLE
JUST
RELEASED
GEMINI
CODE
ASSIST
FOR
VS
CODE
OFFERING
ONE
HUNDRED
AND
EIGHTY
THOUSANDTH
MONTHLY
CODE
COMPLETIONS
AND
SUPPORTING
A
ONE
HUNDRED
AND
TWENTY
EIGHT
THOUSANDTH
TOKEN
CONTEXT
WINDOW
THATS
SOME
SERIOUS
CODING
POWER
RIGHT
THERE
AND
DEEPSEEK
LAUNCHED
DEEPGEMM
AN
FP8
GEMM
LIBRARY
ACHIEVING
ONE
THOUSAND
THREE
HUNDRED
AND
FIFTIETH
TFLOPS
ON
HOPPER
GPUS
LIKE
WHAT
EVEN
IS
THAT
OPENAI
ROLLED
OUT
DEEP
RESEARCH
TO
ALL
PAID
USERS
WITH
VARYING
ACCESS
LEVELS
BASED
ON
SUBSCRIPTION
TIER
AND
THEY
INTRODUCED
ADVANCED
VOICE
POWERED
BY
GPT4O
MINI
TO
FREE
USERS
AS
A
DAILY
PREVIEW
THATS
SOME
FANCY
AI
TECH
RIGHT
THERE
ANTHROPIC
LAUNCHED
THE
WORLDS
FIRST
HYBRID
REASONING
AI
MODEL
LEADING
MULTIPLE
BENCHMARKS
WHATS
NEXT
AI
OVERLORDS
IN
CRYPTO
NEWS
THE
SEC
DROPPED
ITS
INVESTIGATION
AGAINST
UNISWAP
LABS
AND
BITCOIN
ENTERED
A
TECHNICAL
BEAR
MARKET
FALLING
TWENTIETH
FROM
ITS
ALLTIME
HIGH
THATS
SOME
SERIOUS
CRYPTO
DRAMA
RIGHT
THERE
GRAYSCALE
FILED
TO
ALLOW
STAKING
FOR
ITS
SPOT
ETHEREUM
ETF
AND
THE
ETHEREUM
FOUNDATIONS
AYA
MIYAGUCHI
TRANSITIONED
FROM
EXECUTIVE
DIRECTOR
TO
PRESIDENT
WHATS
GOING
ON
IN
THE
ETHEREUM
WORLD
THE
CRYPTO
MARKET
SAW
ONE
HUNDRED
AND
FORTY
EIGHTH
BILLION
LIQUIDATED
IN
TWENTY
FOURTH
HOURS
WITH
BITCOIN
LEADING
THE
DOWNWARD
TREND
THATS
SOME
SERIOUS
MARKET
VOLATILITY
RIGHT
THERE
HACKERS
ARE
USING
FAKE
GITHUB
PROJECTS
TO
STEAL
CRYPTO
WITH
ONE
VICTIM
LOSING
FIFTH
BITCOIN
LIKE
BE
CAREFUL
OUT
THERE
FOLKS
THATS
IT
FOR
TODAYS
DAILY
BRAINROT
FOLKS
STAY
WOKE
KEEP
UP
WITH
THE
TECH
NEWS
AND
DONT
GET
LEFT
BEHIND